A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Art Institute of Chicago, Instructors Exhibition, 1955 - 3.1: Art Institute of Chicago Instructors Exhibition 1955
Art Institute of Chicago, "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," 1956 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, American Painting and Sculpture, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, Instructors Exhibition, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Art Institute of Chicago, "Artists of Chicago and Vicinity," 1961 - 4.1: 1961
Art Institute of Chicago, "Drawing New Conclusions," 1992 - 3.1: "Drawing New Conclusions," Art Institute of Chicago group exhibition 1992
Baja Club, "Art's As Good An Investment as Bonds," New York, 1989 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions 1988-89
Bal Tabarin Room, Sherman Hotel, Chicago 1959 - 4.1: 1950s
Bank One, "Athletes and Heroes," Youngstown, Ohio, 1987 - 4.1: 1987
"Beyond Illustration - The Art of Playboy," Traveling Exhibition, 1971-74 - 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1970s
Blumhelman Gallery and Germans van Eck Gallery, "Artists for Amnesty," New York, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Butler Institute of American Art, "The Artist at Ringside," 1990 - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91, 4.1: 1990
Calgary Inn, "Fall Portfolio of International Artists," Calgary, Alberta, Canada 1980 - 4.1: 1980
Carnegie Institute of Arts, International Exhibition, Pittsburgh, 1955 - 4.1: 1950s
Chicago Navy Pier, Chicago Artists, 1957 - 4.1: 1957
Chicago Public Library, 1958 - 4.1: 1955-59
China Club, "The Famous Show," New York, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
Cig Art
"Cig Art," National Arts Club, New York, 1996 - 4.1: 1996
"Cig Art 2: The Smoke Continues", National Arts Club, New York, 1997 - 3.1: "Cig Art" Benefit Exhibitions 1996-2000
"Cig Art 4: Where There's Smoke", Art Museum of Southern Texas, 2000 - 3.1: "Cig Art" Benefit Exhibitions 1996-2000
Collectors Club Exhibition, 1957 - no materials
Corcoran Gallery of Art, Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Oil Paintings, Washington, DC, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Deer Path Art League Annual Fine Arts Fair, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
El Paso Museum of Art, 1987 - 4.1: 1987
Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, "Grand Opening Group Exhibition," Sarasota, 1980 - 4.1: 1980
Foster Harmon Galleries of American Art, "American Masters Exhibition," Sarasota, FL, annual - 4.1: 1981, 1987
Gimbel's, "Playboy's Art of Fashion Exhibition," Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1979 - 4.2: Grand Palais, "Salon d'Automne," Paris, 1993 - 2.2: Association du Salon d'Automne 1992-99, 4.1: 1993
Greenwich Workshop Gallery, "Greenwich Workshop Gallery Miniature Show '83" - 2.1: 1983, 4.1: 1983
Hammer Galleries, "Group Show of FKH Artists," 1974 - 4.1: 1974
Hammer Galleries, Holiday Exhibitions, New York, 1974 - 4.1: 1974
Hammer Galleries, "Hammer Galleries Graphics," New York, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Hammer Galleries, "Master Prints of the 19th -20th Century," 1987 - 4.1: 1987, V: 1987
Hanson Art Galleries, San Diego, CA - 4.1: 1987
Harmon Gallery, "20th Century American Masters," Naples, FL, 1979 - 4.1: 1979
Illini Union Art Gallery, Illinois 1973 - 4.1: 1973
International Tennis Hall of Fame, "National Exhibition of Tennis Art," 1977 - 3.1: International Tennis Hall of Fame Group Exhibitions 1977-78
International Tennis Hall of Fame, "National Exhibition of Tennis Art," 1978 - 3.1: International Tennis Hall of Fame Group Exhibitions 1977-78
Los Angeles County Fair - see group exhibitions: Millard Sheets Gallery
Marshall Field & Co. Gallery, "Brotherhood in Art," 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
Mickey Mantle's, New York - 4.1: 1988
Midwest Museum of American Art, "Panorama of American Art," Elkhart, IN, 1979 - 4.1: 1979
Millard Sheets Gallery, Fairplex, "Art and the Athlete," Los Angeles County Fair, 1996 - 3.1: "Art and the Athlete" Group Exhibition, Los Angeles County Fair 1996
Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Local Artists' Exhibition, 1952 - 4.1: 1950s
Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Local Artists' Exhibition, 1953 - 4.1: 1950s
Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Local Artists' Exhibition, 1954 - 4.1: 1950s
Minnesota Museum of Art, "TIME Portraits of American Newsmakers," 1969 - 3.1: TIME Magazine Cover Portraits Exhibition, National Portrait Gallery and Minnesota Museum of Art 1969
Minnesota Museum of Art, "Drawings USA 75," St. Paul, 1975 - 4.1: 1975
Minnesota State Fair, 1954 - 4.1: 1950s
Minnesota State Fair, 1955 - 4.1: 1950s
The Monmouth Museum, "The Horse: Man's Noble Companion," Lincroft, NJ 1987 - 4.1: 1987
Museum of the City of New York, "Showstoppers: Great Moments of the American Musical," 1983 - 3.1: Showstoppers Group Exhibition, MCNY 1983
Mystic Seaport Museum, "Archives of American Yachting and Boating," 1985 - 4.1: 1985 National Art Museum of Sport, 1969 - 4.1: 1969
National Portrait Gallery, "TIME Portraits of American Newsmakers," Washington, DC, 1969 - 3.1: TIME Magazine Cover Portraits Exhibition, National Portrait Gallery and Minnesota Museum of Art 1969
Navy Pier Art Show, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
New Orleans Museum of Art, "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy," 1994-95 - 3.1: "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy" traveling exhibition 1995
New-York Historical Society, "That Belmont Look," 1980 - 4.1: 1980
North Mississippi Valley Exhibition, 1964 - 4.1: 1964
North Shore Art League, Chicago Area Show, 1956 - 4.1: 1950s
North Shore Art League, Old Orchard Art Festival, Skokie, IL, 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
North Shore Art League, Old Orchard Art Festival, Skokie, IL, 1959 - 4.1: 1950s ov
Northampton County Area Community College Foundation, 1982 - 4.1: 1982
Odyssey House Art Gallery, New York, 1972 - 4.1: 1972
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago, 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago, 1959 - 4.1: 1950s
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, Chicago, 1965 - 4.1: 1965
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, "Twentieth Anniversary Show," Chicago 1969 - 4.1: 1969
F. Oehlschlaeger Gallery, "American Masters of the 1940s, 50s, and 60s," 1985 - 3.1: "American Masters of the 40s, 50s, and 60s", Frank Oehlschlaeger Gallery, 1985
O'Grady Galleries, "Collectors' Show," 1980 - 4.1: 1980
O'Hana Gallery, "Mixed Christmas Exhibition," London, 1962-63 - 4.1: 1962
Old Orchard Art Festival - see exhibitions: North Shore Art League
Park Shore Gallery, "Director's Choice," Naples, FL, 1990 - 4.1: 1990
Queens Museum of Art, "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy," 1994-95 - 3.1: "Louis Armstrong: A Cultural Legacy" traveling exhibition 1995
Ravinia Festival, 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
San Diego Museum of Art, "Champions: The Olympic Athlete in Art," 1984 - 4.1: 1984
Saratoga Gallery, Saratoga Springs, New York, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Sherman Art Gallery, Paintings and Photographs by Playboy Jazz Artists, 1959 - 4.1: 1950s
Sherman Hotel, Chicago, 1959 - see Bal Tabarin
Spectrum Fine Art, "Ball, Bat, and Glove," New York, 1977 - 3.1: "Ball, Bat, and Glove," Spectrum Fine Art, New York, 1977
Spectrum Fine Art, "Ringside: The Fine Art of Boxing," New York, 1979 - 2.1: 1978, 4.1: 1979
Springfield Art Museum, "Watercolor U.S.A. National Invitational Exhibition," Springfield, MO, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Springfield College, "Women in Sports," 1988 - 4.1: 1988
Steiner & Young Galleries, "20/20 Exhibition," Marietta, Georgia, 1989 - 4.1: 1989
Treasures of Island Creek, Louisville, KY, 1979 - 4.1: 1979
Tunnel Club, "New Perspectives in Contemporary Art," New York, September 1988 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York 1988-89
Tunnel Club, "The Mustache Show", New York, November 1988 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York 1988-89
Tunnel Club, "The Most Famous Artist Alive", New York, December 1988 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions, New York 1988-89
Tunnel Club, "The Greatest Hits Vol 1 Show", New York 1989 - 3.1: Baird Jones' Group Exhibitions 1988-89
University of Southern Florida, "Expose Yourself to Art," 1991 - 4.1: 1991
Whitney Museum, "Americana," New York, 1985 - 4.1: 1985
Yogi Berra Museum, "Viva el Beisbol!" 2000 - 3.1: "Viva el Beisbol!" exhibition, Yogi Berra Museum 2000
Exotic Erotic Halloween Ball - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989, 1996
F
F.I.S.T. - see boxing
F.X. McRory's Whiskey Bar, Seattle, 1980 - see bars
Fairfield Gallery - see exhibitions
Fairmont Hotel - 3.1: Nob Hill, Buena Vista and Bowles Hopkins Gallery 1986
Falstaff, opera by Verdi - 3.1: Falstaff Opera 1993, 4.1: 2002
fan auction - 4.1: 1992
Far Gallery, New York - 3.1: "Recent Graphics and Drawings", The Far Gallery Solo Exhibition 1971
fashion - 3.1: Early Fashion Illustration 1949-57, 3.1: Fashion Illustration for The Domino Catalog 1950s -60s, 3.1: Fashion Illustration for Marshall Field 1957-59 (Oversize only), 4.1: 1958, 1971, undated 1990s
F.D.N.Y. (Fire Department of New York)
F.D.N.Y. Painting - 3.1: F.D.N.Y. Painting 2002
F.D.N.Y Pipes and Drums - 2.1: 1984
Felicie, Inc. - IID: Price Lists 1970s, 1.2
Felt, Irving Mitchell and Elaine - 2.1: 1977, 3.1: Bill Bradley 1978-2000, see Madison Square Garden
Femlin - see Playboy
Festival Internacioal de Danca Contemporanea - 4.1: 2000
Fields, Edward - see tapestry
The Fifth Dimension - 3.1: Fifth Dimension Album Art 1970-1982
Fight of the Century - see boxing
figure skating - 3.1: 1982 U.S. Figure Skating National Championships, V: 1980s, see also Olympic Games
Healey, Kathy - V: Kathy Healey, 1981
Superskates - 2.1: 1981, 4.1: 1981, V: 1980s
United States Figure Skating Association - 2.1: 1984, 3.1: 1982 U.S. Figure Skating National Championships
film - 3.1: Beauty, the Beach, and the Bizarre 1984, 3.1: Houston Film Fest 1990, 3.1: Wine Country Film Fest 1990, 4.1: 1972, 1990, see also Screen Actors Guild
"Ali," 2002 film with Will Smith - 2.1: 2001
"American Rider" motorcycle documentary - 2.1: 1991
"Donnie Darko" 2001 film - 2.1: 2000
The Family Man" 2000 film with Nicholas Cage - 2.1: 1999
"The Ice Storm" 1997 film - 2.1: 1996
"Jerry Maguire" 1997 film with Tom Cruise - 2.1: 1996
"The Lone Ranger", 1978 feature film - 3.1: The Lone Ranger, 1977
"Mr. Baseball," Twentieth Century Fox - 2.1: 1991
"My Old Man," 1979 CBS TV movie - 2.1: 1979, 1990
"Quarterback Princess," Twentieth Century Fox - 2.1: 1983, 1992
Rocky films - 3.1: Rocky films 1980-1990
"Rooster," 1981 - 3.1: "Rooster," 1981
1976 documentary, Twentieth Century Fox - 2.1: 1976
finance
Mr. Neiman's own finances - 2.1: 1975, IID: Invoices Paid, see International Management Group, Inc.
represented in art - see investing, Stock Market, Chicago Board of Trade
Finland - IID: Price Lists 1970s, 3.1: Casa Grafica Solo Exhibition, Helsinki, Finland, 1977
Fireman, Shelly - 3.1: Shelly's New York Restaurant 2000
Firestone, Roy - 4.1: 1986
Fischer, Bobby - 4.1: 1972, 1974, 1987
fishing - see Marlin!
Fittipaldi, Emerson - see auto racing
Fitzgerald, Ella - see jazz
Flagg, Special Agent Warren M. - 4.1: 1998
Florida Racing - 4.1: undated
Floyd, Ray - see golf
Flynt, Larry - 2.1: 1976
Focus Midwest Magazine - 4.1: 1964, 1967, 1970, 1980
Foley, Jaclyn - 4.1: 1996, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002
Folies Bergere - see casinos
food - 3.1: James Beard 1982-87, 3.1: The Culinary Arts exhibition 1998, 4.1: 1981, 1991, 1993, 1994, 1995
Foot Locker - 2.1: 1990
football - search for individual players listed alphabetically
college football
Cross-Town Rivalry, 1967, 1993 - 4.1: 1993
Georgia Tech - 4.1: 1983
Iowa vs. Minnesota, 1982 - 4.1: 1983, 1984
Nebraska Football - 2.1: 1976
Northwestern University - 4.1: 1996
Ohio State Buckeyes, Rivalry, 1975 - 4.1: 2001
Penn State University - 4.1: 1996
Pioneer Bowl - 4.1: 1976, University of California Los Angeles (UCLA)
University of Florida, The Gators, 1995 - 3.1: Florida Gators, 1995
Universities of Iowa - see Iowa vs. Minnesota, 1982
University of Michigan, Rivalry, 1975 - 4.1: 2001
University of Southern California - see football: college: Cross-Town Rivalry, 1967, 1993
University of Texas, The Texas Longhorns, 1985 - 3.1: The Texas Longhorns 1985, 4.1: 1986
University of Minnesota - see Iowa vs. Minnesota, 1982
University of Nebraska, The Devaney Era serigraph suite - 2.1: 1997, 4.1: 1974, 1975, 1988, 1992
Football Game, 1960s - 4.1: 1998
Game of the Century, 1983 - 4.1: 1983
Gridiron Football News - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-73
NFL football - 4.1: 1967, 1968, 1969, 1970, 1972, 1973, 1974, 1975, 1976, 1977 ov, 1978, 1982, 1985, 1988, 1991, 1992, 1996
Buffalo Bills - 3.1: O.J. Simpson, 4.1: 1972, see also football: Superbowl XXVIII
Dallas Cowboys - 2.3: March 1993, 4.1: 1972 and ov, 1976, 1978, 1979, 1982, 1984, 1989, 1994, see also Superbowl XXVIII
Denver Broncos - see Superbowl XXII, 3.1: John Elway, 1999, 4.1: 1972, 1978, 1999
etchings - 4.1: 1976
Giants-Broncos Classic - 4.1: 1988
Green Bay Packers - 4.1: 1992, 1997
In the Pocket, 1988 - see football: Superbowl XXII
Kansas City Chiefs - 4.1: 1997
Legends Magazine - see NFL Alumni
Miami Dolphins - 4.1: 1972 and ov, 1993
Minnesota Vikings - 4.1: 1975, 1977
Mirage Bowl - 4.1: 1978
NFL Alumni - 4.1: 1990, 1991, 1992
Legends Official Magazine of the NFL Alumni - 4.2: Legends NFL Alumni Magazine, 1982-2002
NFL Alumni Player of the Year Awards Dinner - 4.1: 1983, 1984, 1985, 1987
Yearbooks - 4.1: 1980
NFL Players Association - 4.1: 1974
New England Patriots - 4.1: 1997, 2004, 2005
New York Giants - 4.1: 1987, 1998, 1999, 2002, 2003
New York Jets - 2.1: 1980, 3.1: New York Jets 1966 -, 3.1: Hammer Galleries Exhibition of NY Jets Drawings, 1968
Oakland Raiders - 4.1: 1977
Pittsburgh Steelers - 4.1: 1975, 1979
San Francisco 49ers - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91, 1.2: Bowles Galleries 1991, 4.1: 1982, 1990
Superbowl, general - 3.1: Countdown to Superbowl by Dave Anderson 1969, 4.1: 1997
Superbowl stamps - see stamps or U.S. Postal Service
Superbowl II, 1969 - 4.1: 1969 and ov
Superbowl V, 1972 - 4.1: 1972 and ov
Superbowl VI, 1973 - 4.1: 1973 and ov, 4.2: Playboy 1973, see Appendix E
Superbowl IX, 1975 - 4.1: 1975 ov
Superbowl X, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Superbowl XI, 1977 - 4.1: 1977
Superbowl XII, 1978 - 3.1: Superbowl XII, 1978, 4.1: 1983
Superbowl XIX, 1985 - 3.1: Superbowl XIX, 1985
Superbowl XXI, 1987 - 4.1: 1988
Superbowl XXII, In the Pocket, 1988 - 3.1: Superbowl XXII painting In the Pocket, at Allyson Louis Gallery 1988, 4.1: 1989 ov
Superbowl XXIII, 1989, Superplay, 1989 - 2.1: 1989, 3.1: Superbowl XXIII painting, Superplay, 1989
Superbowl XXIV, Silverdome Superbowl, 1990 - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91
Superbowl XXV, 1991 - 4.1: 1991
Superbowl XXVII, 1993 - 2.1: 1993
Superbowl XXVIII, 1994 - 3.1: Superbowl XXVIII, 1994
Superbowl XXX, 1996 - 2.1: 1997, see exhibitions
Superbowl XXXVIII, 2002 - 4.1: 2002
Superbowl XXXIX, 2003 - 4.1: 2003
Superplay - see football: Superbowl XXIII, 1989
Washington Redskins - 4.1: 1972, see also football: Superbowl XXII
foreign language articles, Finnish - 4.1: 1977, Italian - see auto racing
Foreman, George - see boxing
forgery - 2.3: Imitations and Forgeries, 4.1: 1989, 1994, 1995 ov, see also theft and vandalism
Forrester, Bruce (event photographer) - see photograph files for Bowles/Sorokko Gallery openings
Foster Harmon Gallery of American Art - 2.1: 1975, 1977, 1978, 1979, 1980, 1989, 1992, 1993, 4.1: 1974, see also exhibitions
Fouch-Roseboro Corporation - 2.1: 1976
Fouquet's - see restaurants
Fox, Manheim - 2.1: 1979
Fox, Virgil - 4.1: 1965
Fran Joswick Therapeutic Riding Center - 4.1: 1998
Francis, Emile - 4.1: 1975
Franey Langkop, Dorothy - V: 1990s
Frank, Morris - 4.1: 1975
Franklin Bowles Gallery - see Bowles Galleries
Franklin Pierce College - 1.1: Honorary Degrees
fraud - see forgery
Frazier, Joe - see boxing
Fred Dorfman, Inc. - 2.1: 1978
Freeman, Morgan - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Freidman, Joann - 2.1: 1978
French Riviera - 4.2: Playboy 1962, see Appendix E, see also Monaco
Friars' Club - 1.1: New York Friar's Club
Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson Attorneys - 2.2: Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson Attorneys, 1.2: Lawsuit Against Felicie, Inc.
Frito Lay - 2.1: 1991
Frost, David - see golf
Fujita family - 2.2: Tele Planning International, Tokyo 1993-98
G
Gable, Dan - 3.1: American Sportscasters Association Hall of Fame Awards Dinner 1984 -present
Galerie Borjeson, Malmo, Sweden - 3.1: Sweden Exhibitions 1976-77
Galice, Christina - see Christina Galice Gallery
Gallagher's Steak House - see restaurants
La Galleria d'Arte - 2.2: La Galleria d'Arte, see also exhibitions
Gallery 100 - 2.1: 1979
Gallery Mack, Seattle - 2.1: 1979, 1983, 1985, 1987, 4.1: 1974, 1981, see also exhibitions
Gallery One, Denver, Colorado - see exhibitions
Gallo, Bill - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: Gallagher's Steak House - The Neiman Collection 2002, 4.1: 2002
gambling - see casinos
Game of the Century, 1983 - see football
Ganassi, Cara and Chip - 2.1: 1994, 1995
Gardiner, John - 2.1: 1975, 3.1: Heit Galleries Solo Exhibition, Phoenix 1976
Garret, Lesly - 4.1: 1982
Garvey, Steve - 2.1: 1979, 1981, 1983, 1986, 1989, 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions, 4.1: undated 1980s, 1980, 1988, 1989, VII: Bags
Gene Michael Fund - 4.1: 1994
General Electric - see promotions
General Mills - 3.1: Wheaties 1997
Gere, Gary - see The Taxicab Chronicles
Germany, Baden Baden - 2.1: 1986, 1987, 1988
Gibson Guitars - 2.1: 1997
"Art of Guitars II" exhibition - 3.1: Gibson "Art of Guitars II" 2000
The Gifts of Music, 1994 - 4.1: 1994
Gilbert, Rod - 4.1: 1992
Rod Gilbert, 1968 drawing - 4.1: 1992
Rod Gilbert, 1974 drawing - 4.1: 1974
Rod Gilbert, 1976 - 4.1: 1976, 1992
Giorgio Beverly Hills - 2.1: 1985
Giulianni, Mayor Rudy - 3.1: Mayor Giulianni and NYC Advisory Commission for Cultural Affairs, 1994-2001
Givenchy - 3.1: Givenchy 1999
Gleason, Jackie - see The Hustler
Goff, Bill - see Spectrum Fine Art
Gold Glove Award - 4.1: 1992
Goldberg, Whoopie - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Golden Apple Awards - 2.1: 1990, 4.1: 1977, 1990, 1995, 1996
Golden Boy - see musicals
golf - 3.1: Jack Nicklaus and Arnold Palmer 1973-74, 4.1: 1973, 1987, 1988-89, 1990, 1993, 1995, 1997, 2000, 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992
16th at Cypress, 1983 - 3.1: 43rd Crosby, 1984, 4.1: 1982
An Queens Cup, Japan - 2.1: 1990, 4.1: 1990 and ov
Atlanta National Golf Club
Atlanta National Golf Club California Merlot - 2.1: 1996, 2000, 4.1: 1996
Augusta
The 16th at Augusta, 1992 - 2.1: 1996, 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999
April at Augusta, 1990 - 4.1: 1990, 1995
Arnold Palmer and Richard Pack, Augusta Clubhouse Bar, 1973 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002
Bethpage Black, The 18th at Bethpage Black - 3.1: U.S. Open at Bethpage Black 2002, 4.1: 2002
caddies - 4.1: 1976
Crosby National Pro-Am Golf Championship - 3.1: Hanson Galleries New Orleans and Carmel, 1983-84, 3.1: 43rd Crosby National Pro-Am, 1984
Excalibur Classic, Palm Springs - 2.1: 2001, 3.1: Pebble Beach 1982-1995
Floyd, Ray - 4.1: 1987
Frank Sinatra Celebrity Golf Tournament - 4.1: 1998
Frost, David
David Frost Wines - 3.1: David Frost Wines 1998-2003
Gavea Golf and Country Club, Rio de Janeiro
Gavea Golf and Country Club, Rio de Janeiro, 1985 (also appears as International Golf Foursome) - 2.1: 1985, 4.1: 2001
golf bars - 4.2: Bartender Magazine, 1993-2002
Golf Courses Calendar 1996 - VII: Artifacts 1996
Golf Digest Magazine - 2.1: 1972, 1974, 1976, 4.1: 1976, 2000
Golf Winners, 1984 - 3.1: Advertising Layouts 1980s, 4.1: 1984, 1986
Golf's Threesome - 3.1: Advertizing Layouts 1980s, 4.1: 1979
Harbour Town, 18th at Harbour Town - 4.1: 2000
International Golf Foursome, 1985 - see Gavea Golf and Country Club
International Golfer - 4.1: 1994
International Golf Leisure and Lifestyle Magazine - 4.1: 2001
Joe Pagliei Invitational - 4.1: 1985
Masters - 4.1: 1990
Mystic Rock at Nemacolin Woodlands - 4.1: 1995
Natural Golfer Magazine - 4.1: 2000
Nicklaus, Jack - 3.1: Jack Nicklaus and Arnold Palmer 1973 -74, 4.1: 1972, 1983, 1990
The Golden Bear, 1992 painting and serigraph - 4.1: 1993, VII
Oakmont, 1983 U.S. Open, Oakmont, 1983 - 3.1: 1983 U.S. Open, Oakmont, 1983, 3.1: Hanson Galleries New Orleans and Carmel, 1983-84
Robert H. Ogle Invitational - 2.1: 2000, 4.1: 1998
Palmer, Arnold - 2.1: 1978, 3.1: Jack Nicklaus and Arnold Palmer 1973-74, 4.1: 1983
Arnie in the Rain, 1973 - 2.1: 1975, 1978, 4.1: 1974
Arnold Palmer and Richard Pack, Augusta Clubhouse Bar, 1973 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002
Pebble Beach Golf Club
18th at Pebble Beach - 3.1: Pebble Beach 1982-1995, 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1997-2002, 4.1: 1984, 2001, 2002
The Lodge at Pebble Beach, 1995 - 3.1: Pebble Beach 1982-1995, 4.1: 1995
pens - see Promotions - S.T. Dupont LeRoy Neiman Golf Pens
Pinehurst - 4.1: 2002
Piping Rock Golf Club - 4.1: 1993, 2002
Player, Gary
Gary Player, 1971 drawing - 3.1: Rotonda Superstars 1973-75
Rodriguez, Chi Chi - 4.1: 1973
Royal Golf - Club de Belgique
Chateau de Ravenstein, 1968 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002
Sara Lee Classic - 4.1: 1993, 1994
Sarazen, Gene - 3.1: David Frost Wines 1998-2003
Shinnecock Hills - 4.1: 1995
The 18th at Shinnecock or The Home Hole at Shinnecock - 2.1: 2001, 4.1: 1995, 2002
Six Golfers - see Golf Winners
Snead, Sam
Sam Snead - 3.1: David Frost Wines 1998-2001
Southampton U.S.P.G.A. Open - 4.1: 1984, 1986
Spyglass, #1 at Spyglass - 4.1: 1991, 1999
St. Andrews, Scotland - 4.1: 1987
The Clubhouse at Old St. Andrews, 1988 serigraph - 2.1: 1988, 3.1: Steiner & Young Galleries Exhib 1989, 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 4.1: 1995, 1998, 2002
The Jigger Inn Bar - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002 St. Cloud
Clubhouse Bar at St. Cloud, 1990 - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1993-2002
U.S. Open - 4.1: 1977, see also golf: Oakmont
Valhalla - 4.1: 2000
Vintage
Vintage Charities - 4.1: undated 1980s
Vintage Invitational - 2.1: 1986, 4.1: 1986, 1988
Vintage Cove
The Cove at Vintage - 2.1: 1988, 3.1: Hanson Art Galleries, 1986, 4.1: undated 1980s, 1989 ov
Vintage Palm Springs, Sam Snead Teeing Off at Vintage Palm Springs - 4.1: 2001
Wall Street Charity Fund Pro-Am Golf Tournament - 4.1: 2002
Westchester - 4.1: 1981, 1989, 1993
Winged Foot Golf Club - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, Publicity and Related Exhibitions, 4.1: 1997
The 18th at Winged Foot - 4.1: 2002
Winged Foot, 1996 - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999
The Wonderful World of Professional Golf by Mark H. McCormack, cover illustration by LeRoy Neiman - 4.1: 1973 and ov
Woods, Tiger - 4.1: 1997, 1999, Playboy 1998
Golota, Andrew - 4.1: 1996
Gone with the Wind, 1989 - 3.1: Gone with the Wind perfume promotion 1989, 4.1: 2004
Gonzalez, Jorge Luis - 4.1: 1995
Gonzmart, Cesar - 2.1: 1991, 1992, 4.1: 1992
Good Tidings Foundation - 3.1: Good Tidings Foundation LeRoy Neiman Art Centers, 1998-present, 3.1: Joe DiMaggio 1998
Gooden, Dwight - 4.1: 2001
Goodman, Dr. Margaret - 3.1: Ringside and Training Principles by Goodman and Homansky 2001
Goodwill Games - 2.1: 1989, 3.1: Goodwill Games Moscow 1986, 3.1: Goodwill Games 1998
Gore, Al - 2.1: 1987, 3.2: Big Time Golf, 1992, 4.1: 1992
Gourmet Gala - see March of Dimes
Grady, John - 2.1: 1976
John Grady, Midnight Mass, 1988 drawing - 4.1: 1990
Graham, Martha - see dance
Grand Ballroom, 1987 etching - 4.1: 1987
Le Grand Escalier de L'Opera, 1969 - 1.2: Knoedler: Serigraph Release Ads, 2.1: 1996
grand prix - see auto racing
Grant, Michael - see boxing
Gray, Anthony John - 3.1: Palm Springs Commemorative Coin
Graziano, Rocky - see boxing
Great American Workout - 2.1: 1990
Great Gatsby's Auction House - 4.1: 1998
Great Irish Fair, NY 1982 - 3.1: The Great Irish Fair poster 1982
Green, Rev. Al - 3.1: Blues Ball 1997-2004
Greene, "Mean Joe" - 2.1: 1981
Greenberg, Hank - 4.1: 1968
Greenspan, Bud - 2.1: 2000
Greenwich Workshop Gallery - see exhibitions: group
Gregory, Cynthia - see ballet
Gregory, Jack - 2.2: Jack Gregory 1993-1998
Gretzky, Wayne
The Great Gretzky, 1981 - 3.1: Wayne Gretzky 1981-2002
Wayne Gretzky, 2002 - 3.1: Wayne Gretzky 1981-2002
Gridiron Football News - see football
Griese (Miami Dolphins quarterback 1972) - 4.1: 1972
Griffey, Ken - see Skoal Pinch Hitter
Griffin, Merv - see television
Grosset and Dunlap Inc. Publishers - 3.2. LeRoy Neiman Art and Lifestyle, 1974, Felicie, Correspondence